Joshua Langer

3335 93rd Curve Blaine, MN 55449 (612) 723-4971 joshuarllanger@gmail.com GitHub - LinkedIn - Site github.com/JoshuaLanger linkedin.com/in/josh-r-langer www.joshlanger.me

SUMMARY

Front-end web developer skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and Git. Experienced in developing and designing websites and applications using both front-end and back-end technologies. Persistent, resourceful, and punctual creator who works well alone and with a team.

SKILLS

HTML5 React Issue Resolution Client Relationship CSS3, Sass Git Knowledge and Resource Management JavaScript (ES6) UI/UX Design Procurement Team Collaboration

PROJECTS

Personal Site | Jan 2019

Designed site using Figma and CodePen to display projects, skills, and contact information.

• Built on Virtual Studio Code, styled with Sass 7-1 architecture.

Quick Draw! (quick-draw.app)

July 2018

- A game that tests reflexes and returns a total score.
- Built with the React and styled-components libraries.

Dakota Learning App

Sept 2015 - Dec 2015

- Designed app over several iterations based on research and user feedback.
- Built with Android SDK.

EXPERIENCE

Client Support Representative

April 2018 – January 2019

Target, Brooklyn Park, MN

- Resolved technical and procedural issues for Target employees, prioritizing a speedy recovery in under 5 minutes to improve productivity.
- Contributed to knowledge base and trends in weekly peer meetings.

Computer Lab Technician

March 2017—January 2018

Anoka-Ramsey Community College, Coon Rapids, MN

- Solved technical issues at IT help desk and over phone from students and faculty.
- Worked as part of a team to coordinate deliveries or resolve issues.

EDUCATION

University of Minnesota

Graduated 2016

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

- Studied several concepts such as web development, software development, algorithms, object-oriented design, and UI/UX design.
- Developed several programs on own and with a team.